[
  {
    "id": "699",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which database service is a MySQL compatible relational database engine that combines the speed and availability of high-end comercial databases with the simplicity and cost effectiveness of open source databases?",
      "answers": [
        "Elasticache",
        "RedShift",
        "Aurora",
        "MariaDB",
        "PostgeSQL",
        "MySql",
        "SQL Server",
        "Oracle"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Aurora"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "700",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With Aurora, you start with a ______ database and scale by _______ increments up to ______ in size?",
      "answers": [
        "10Gb, 10Gb, 64Tb",
        "10Gb, 5Gb, 64Tb",
        "10Gb, 5Gb, 32Tb",
        "5Gb, 5Gb, 16Tb",
        "10Gb, 10Gb, 128Tb"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["10Gb, 10Gb, 64Tb"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "701",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With Aurora, you your storage _______?",
      "answers": [
        "auto-scales",
        "scales through manual intervention"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["auto-scales"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "702",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With Aurora, compute resources can scale up to _______?",
      "answers": [
        "32vCPUs and 244Gb of storage",
        "16vCPUs and 256Gb of storage",
        "16vCPUs and 244Gb of storage",
        "64vCPUs and 128Gb of storage"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["32vCPUs and 244Gb of storage"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "703",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With Aurora, you can scale with no downtime?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "704",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With Aurora, you can have _______ copies of your database in each AZ?",
      "answers": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "4",
        "1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["2"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "705",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With Aurora, you can 2 copies of your database in each AZ, with a minimum of ______ AZs?",
      "answers": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "4",
        "1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["3"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "706",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Aurora is designed to transparently handle the loss of up to _______ copies of your database without affecting write availability?",
      "answers": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "4",
        "1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["2"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "706",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Aurora is designed to transparently handle the loss of up to _______ copies of your database without affecting read availability?",
      "answers": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "4",
        "1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["3"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "707",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Aurora storage is ________?",
      "answers": [
        "self-healing",
        "self-deprecating",
        "self-promoting",
        "auto-scaling"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["self-healing"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "708",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Aurora storage is self-healing by _________?",
      "answers": [
        "continuously scanning data blocks and disks for errors and then repairing them automatically",
        "continuously scanning data blocks and disks for errors and then removing failed devices",
        "continuously scanning data blocks and disks for errors and then promoting healthy devices",
        "continuously scanning data blocks and disks for errors and then alerting AWS to repair the failed devices"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["continuously scanning data blocks and disks for errors and then repairing them automatically"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "709",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Which of these are the two types of Aurora replicas?",
      "answers": [
        "Aurora Replicas",
        "MySQL Read Replicas",
        "Multi-AZ Read Replicas",
        "Multi-Zone Read Replicas"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Aurora Replicas", "MySQL Read Replicas"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "710",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Up to how many Aurora Read Replicas can you have?",
      "answers": [
        "15",
        "5",
        "10",
        "3"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["15"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "711",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Up to how many MySQL Read Replicas can you have?",
      "answers": [
        "15",
        "5",
        "10",
        "3"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["5"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "712",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of Aurora read replica can you auto failover to?",
      "answers": [
        "Aurora Read Replicas",
        "MySQL Read Replicas"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Aurora Read Replicas"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "713",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS DB platform is most suitable for OLTP?",
      "answers": [
        "Elasticache",
        "RDS/DynamoDB",
        "Redshift"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["RDS/DynamoDB"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "714",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When replicating data from your primary RDS instance to your secondary RDS instance, what is the charge?",
      "answers": [
        "Double the standard data transfer charge",
        "Same as the standard data transfer charge",
        "No Charge, Its free",
        "Half of the standard data transfer charge"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["No Charge, Its free"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "715",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS service is best suited for non relational databases?",
      "answers": [
        "RDS",
        "RedShift",
        "DynamoDB",
        "Elasticache"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["DynamoDB"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "716",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you add a rule to an RDS security group you do not need to specify a port number or protocol?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "717",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "If you are using Amazon RDS Provisioned IOPS storage with MySQL and Oracle database engines what is the maximum size RDS volume you can have by default?",
      "answers": [
        "500GB",
        "1TB",
        "3TB",
        "6TB",
        "5TB"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["6TB"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "718",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What happens to the I/O operations while you take a database snapshot?",
      "answers": [
        "I/O operations to the database are suspended for the duration of the snapshot",
        "Nothing",
        "I/O operations to the database are sent to a Replica (if available) for the duration of the snapshot",
        "I/O operations will be functioning normally"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["I/O operations to the database are suspended for the duration of the snapshot"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "719",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What AWS service is best used for Business Intelligence Tools/Data Warehousing?",
      "answers": [
        "Elastic Beanstalk",
        "Elasticache",
        "DynamoDB",
        "RedShift"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["RedShift"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "720",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In RDS when using multiple availability zones, can you use the secondary database as an independent read node?",
      "answers": [
        "No",
        "Only in US-West-1",
        "Depends on how you set it up",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["No"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "721",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Amazon's Elasticache uses which two engines?",
      "answers": [
        "Redis & Memory",
        "Reddit & Memcrush",
        "Redis & Memcached",
        "MyISAM & InnoDB"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Redis & Memcached"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "722",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Databases",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "By default, the maximum provisioned IOPS capacity on an Oracle and MySQL RDS instance (using provisioned IOPS) is 30,000 IOPS.",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  }
]
